Ikite ikite ikitsukuse
Live, live on, with all your might
Hikari o mirai e
Follow the light to the future
Uragirareta kodoku na sekai ni torinokosare
Betrayed and left behind in this lonely world
Miushinatta ashita o osorete ima mo
Fearing a tomorrow I've lost sight of
Ibasho o sagasu
I search for the place I belong
Hitsuyou to saretai kokoro no sakebi
My heart screams out, "I want to be needed"
Karamiau IDENTITY tashikametainda shinjite iikana
I want to puzzle out these entwined identities, but can I trust them?
Ikite ikite ikitsukuse
Live, live on, with all your might
Hikari o mirai e
Follow the light to the future
Tatoe subete ushinattemo
Even if you lose everything
Kibou o tsunaide
Stay connected to hope
Boku ga koko ni iru imi
I don't know why I'm here
Ima wa wakaranakute mo ii
But that's all right with me right now
Kimi to waraiaeru you ni
I have to overcome and press on
Jibun de tachikitte susumudake
So I can smile with you again
Remember, the Work Trip is First and Foremost a Learning Opportunity (Part 1)
Yay! Vacation, vacation!
Lily, we are not here to enjoy ourselves.
This is a learning opportunity for us all.
Oh, please. We're not going
to learn anything while we're having fun.
You've only been officially employed with us
for a month. How could you know that?
Because I've been on lots of
'work learning opportunity' trips,
and they all end up being fun vacations.
It won't be any different with the Demon Army.
This is why I hired you, Leo.
Your wealth of experience is invaluable.
But can you still claim that after seeing this?
It's hella run down!
Goodness.
I like it! This place has quite the character!
Mernes, you chose this place, yes?
Yeah. It's got four walls and
a roof and it's deserted. It's perfect.
THAT'S how you picked a place to stay?
I see nothing wrong with it.
If the public learned the leaders of the Demon Army
were gathering here, they would panic.
It's imperative that we lie low for the duration of our trip.
That makes sense. No one will find out
who we are at an inn this deserted.
And I told Shutina to book us
under false names to help with that.
I did tell you, didn't I?
Welcome, great leaders of the Demon Army!
Well, the cat's out of the bag now!
I'm so sorry!
Sheesh!
Come now, it's all right!
Thanks for having us!
We're so glad to have you.
We have a lovely outdoor spring for you
to bathe in. I highly recommend it.
An outdoor spring! That sounds nice.
We've no hot springs to bathe in at the castle.
I may need to soak in the spring with a glass of ale.
Hey, what's a 'spring'? Is it like a bath?
Yes, but bigger.
Can I swim in it?
No.
Why not?! I wanna go swimming!
Let's focus, everyone.
We are here to work, remember?
If I could just have a representative
for your group sign here...
Yes, of course.
There. Thank you.
You're very welcome.
Excuse me.
I should inform you that you may encounter
unwanted visitors during your stay.
Huh? What do you mean?
Ghosts.
What?!
Gh-ghosts?!
I'm sure the rumor is merely
the result of a misunderstanding,
but in the case that it isn't, please keep that in mind.
Oh, no! Will we be okay? Can we fight ghosts?!
I-I don't know...
Ghosts don't exist. It's just superstition. All superstition!
Y-yes! And if we do encounter one,
I will destroy it with a spell!
Worry not, Lily!
Oh, good! I feel better now!
If only it were just superstition...
Delicious! This is good stuff.
The food and amenities are wonderful, too.
Great job finding this inn, Mernes.
Thanks.
We still haven't done anything work-related, though.
Isn't this a learning opportunity?
We spent an hour discussing work!
That is more than enough for today.
Oh, c'mon! This is 100% just a vacation!
Cease your prattling! We are Army leaders on
a journey, not a vacation. My goodness.
Queen Echidna?
I am going for a walk, and to purchase some snacks.
Shall I accompany you?
Yeah, what if you run into a ghost?
She won't.
That's right. I'd forgotten to give you something.
The innkeep gave us these charms
of protection. Take one.
Charms?
These.
You gotta be kidding me!
She says they are ghost-dispelling charms that
have been passed down here for generations.
Ghost-dispelling charms... You're sure?
I am. We wouldn't want to be attacked by spirits, after all.
Do ensure you wear them at all times.
Okay!
Very well.
Look, I have four ears!
Uh-huh.
These things dispel ghosts? Come on. I'm gonna pass.
Ah, I see, you're going to pass, are you?
Then I suppose we should have
another private drinking party, you and I!
Seeing as we seemingly need to strengthen our--
I'll wear them with pride, Your Highness!
Get them on! Your Queen commands it!
We need to wear them, too?
They will look flattering on the women, but can you say
the same for us men?
Orders from the boss!
Keep your head down and obey, Edvard.
This is harassment.
You all look wonderful!
On that note...
With these, I will be fine to move about on my own.
Do not remove the charms, now, yes?
Okay!
Yes, ma'am.
Echidna's been gone a while.
Pass.
You think she blacked out somewhere?
Surely you jest. Echidna's tolerance
for liquor is that of a bottomless pit.
Why're there three of you, Leo?
Meanwhile, this one's punch-drunk on catnip juice.
Catnip does have that affect on canines.
Pass.
I'm gonna go check on her.
Don't ditch 'cause you're losing!
I'm not. I just won.
Will you be all right on your own?
There are no ghosts here.
Shutina... Are you afraid of ghosts?
O-of course not! I'm just being careful in
the one in a million chance there's danger!
Uh-huh. I'll be back.
I'm getting pretty tired of playing Tycoon,
so let's take a break.
How about another drink then, Leo?
You still have it in you, yes?
You've been doing nothing BUT drinking this whole time.
Well, of course! This is a special occasion,
why not share it with good friends and drink?
Tonight, we shall drink until we are sated!
Don't drink too much, now.
What's wrong?
Nothing, just... That.
Leo?
Did it move?
O-of course not! You must be seeing things!
Who's there? Echidna? Mernes?
I'm going to take a look.
Queen Echidna and Mernes have both been absent for a
while.
I must assure their safety.
No, you can't! Acting without permission
will destroy the chain of command!
It's tough to figure out what to do
when your boss isn't around.
Hello! Anyone here?
I know not your intentions,
but you should not play pranks on--
Edvard! Huh?
Hey! Stop messing around and open up!
That's right! You're not the type to joke around...
Th-the light!
There's no such thing as ghosts!
I'm sure there's a logical expl...
What was that?!
Ow! What is this?! What is going on?
Ugh! Where is it coming from?!
Shutina, over here!
What's that? Is THAT... a ghost?
Whoa.
That's a rotary phone.
An artifact from the Mechanical Age.
Humans used these before I was born.
What's it doing here?
Allow me to silence it.
Enis la fide sol...
O wind, bring forth utter quiet!
Silence!
Huh?
Yo.
S-silence!
Silence!
O wind, bring forth utter quiet!
Utter quiet!
Now YOU need to be quiet!
Leo, my spell isn't working! What do we do now?!
Fine, I'll try. Silence.
Huh?
Leo! Do something, please!
Can both of you shut up?!
You try, Lily!
It's a ghost!
Look, Lily, listen close. Ghosts aren't real.
They're just superstition.
No, we have plenty of proof.
This was the work of a spirit.
C'mon!
When I was young, we read
a tome about ghosts and spirits.
Ghosts are the strongest human monster.
You can't see them and magic doesn't
work on them. They're invincible.
Ghosts may exist even in the Demon World!
We might be in trouble, Echidna!
What if one of these things attacks us?!
Not to worry! If spells don't work,
then we shall punch it to death!
But how do we punch something we can't see?
It's all right, Shutina.
Ghosts are formidable enemies,
but I will protect you from them!
Echidna...
You see?! We'll be all right.
A ghost may be among us,
but Queen Echidna will keep us safe!
Help us, Echidna!
Why'd you make things more complicated,
you bumbling idiot succubus!
Excuse me?!
Yeah, I said it! You're an adult,
it's your job to calm Lily down!
Generals!
Are you all right?
Queen Echidna!
We're in danger! My spells aren't working,
and strange things keep happening!
I've encountered strange happenings as well.
I cannot find anyone in this inn.
Not the innkeep nor her staff.
It's as if they never existed to begin with.
N-no...
I know it's dififcult to believe, but it's likely a ghost.
Where are the other three Generals?
You didn't run into them?!
No.
That's weird. Mernes and Edvard
went out looking for you.
Wait, three?
Lily?! Hey, Lily! Where'd you go?!
D-did the ghost take Lily!?
This is growing dire.
Shutina! Leo! We must find our colleagues at once!
Yes, ma'am!
To Be Continued